快看
Aw, look.
爺爺奶奶一定為你準備了有趣的一天
I bet Grandma and Grandpa have a fun day planned for you.
沒  沒有  我們不能照看喜旺
No, we don't. We can't watch Hope.
而且  你需要幫我們照看曾奶奶
In fact, you need to watch Maw Maw for us.
你媽和我要去參加
Your mother and I are competing
納什維爾的扛老婆大賽
in the Natesville Wife Carrying Competition.
大塊頭喬和他的矮鬼老婆離婚了
Big Joe and his dwarf wife got divorced.
所以我們今年很有希望獲勝
So we really have a shot this year.
不是吧  爹媽  這不公平
Come on, guys. No fair.
上周末就是我替你們照看曾奶奶的
I watched Maw Maw for you last weekend.
多年來  我爸媽已經摸索出一套獨門秘籍
Over the years, my parents had developed a little strategy
來達成他們的目的
to get what they wanted.
他們稱之為
They called it
"紅臉警  白臉警"
"Bad Cop, Sad Cop."
你敢停我們家的煤氣
You turn off our gas,
老娘就讓你變成一個加氣站的充氣員
I'll have you busted down to pumping gas.
你不能停掉我們家的煤氣
You can't turn off our gas.
這只雞還沒烤熟呢
This rotisserie chicken is barely cooked.
人家吃生肉會死掉的
If we eat this, we'll die!
如果你不讓我們進去  我就讓你從一個
If you don't let us in, I'll have you busted down
檢票員變成"檢尿員"
from checking credentials to checking urinal cakes.
遺愿基金會說有免費票送給我們的
The Last Wish Foundation said there'd be tickets for us.
老娘就讓你從一個
I will have you busted down
交通女警變成一個家庭女傭
from meter maid to regular maid.
我可告訴你  野餐都用不起桌布
And trust me, that is a picnic without a blanket.
我們也就遲到了62分鐘而已
We're barely 62 minutes late.
求你了  我丟了工作  我的狗狗也死了
Please, I lost my job. My dog died.
我最好的朋友上戰場后再也沒回來
My best friend didn't make it back from the war...
是減肥之戰
on obesity.
我不會把你們的車拖走的
I'm not gonna tow your car.
我只是很遺憾沒辦法收回那張罰單
The only thing I regret is not being able to take back that ticket.
如果你不照顧曾奶奶
If you don't watch Maw Maw,
老娘就把你變成繼子
I will bust you down to stepchild.
如果你覺得你之前的待遇已經夠糟糕了
And if you think you had it bad before,
那是因為你還沒見識真正的慘狀
you ain't seen nothing yet.
你剛剛吐在咖啡桌上了
You just spit on the coffee table.
吉米  求你了
Jimmy, please?
業務慘淡
Business is slow.
我也沒有退休儲蓄
I have no retirement savings.
我兒子是個廢物
My son's a disappointment.
好吧  當然了
Well, yes, of course.
我愿意替你們照看曾奶奶
I'll-I'll watch Maw Maw for you.
太棒了
Great.
我們很晚才會回來
We'll be out late.
我們絕對可以去當警察
We totally could've been cops.
讓這座城市純凈無瑕
We'd clean this city up.
你們好啊  吉斯一家
Hello, Chances.
謝謝你親自上門拜訪  沃利
Thank you for meeting us at the house, Wally.
沒什么
Not a problem.
我剛在街角的老巫女那洗完牙
The old voodoo woman who whitens my teeth lives around the corner.
這是我形象改造的一部分
It's part of my makeover.
你們覺得我看上去多大了  等等  等等
How old do you think I look? Whoa, whoa!
不準說錯
There's no wrong answer.
-72歲  -錯
- 72. - Wrong answer.
你干啥要這么折騰自己
Why are you trying to euthanize yourself?
我手頭有個大案子
I've got a big case
那個檢察官雇了兩個"美律"
and the prosecutor has hired two young "LILFs"
來動搖陪審團
to sway the jury.
美律是指"我想調戲的美女律師"
"Lawyers I'd Like to Frolic with."
不是吧  各位  這是不言自明的
Come on, guys. It's self-explanatory.
我能理解
Makes sense to me.
我們都知道OJ辛普森是有罪的
Like we knew O.J. was guilty
指辛普森涉嫌殺妻案  瑪莎為首席檢察官
因為瑪莎·克拉克實在太性感了
because Marcia Clark was so hot.
我對那個案子不熟
I'm not familiar with that case.
但閑話扯夠了
But enough small talk.
我15分鐘后要去做蜜蠟修眉了
I have to get to my eyebrow wax in 15 minutes.
你們這次又犯什么事了
What did you guys do now?
我們可什么事都沒犯
We didn't do anything.
實際上  這次犯事的人是我
Actually, this time, it's me.
你在水族館一定會玩得很開心的
Oh, you are gonna have so much fun at the aquarium.
好了
All right.
我就在這兒等你回來 好嗎
And I'll be right here when you get back, okay?
吉斯太太  抱歉
Oh, uh, Mrs. Chance, I'm sorry.
我不能讓喜旺上車
I can't let Hope on the bus.
她的同意書必須由法定監護人來簽
Her permission slip needs to be signed by a legal guardian.
我跟她爸已經結婚了  所以沒事
Oh, well, I'm married to her father, so...
不  抱歉
No, I'm sorry.
為了孩子們的安全考慮
It's for the kids' safety.
真的嗎
Really.
你有臉說這話
Says the person
你都雇了個在臉上穿孔
who hired the psycho with the face piercings
又搞淚痕紋身的神經病來開車呢
and the teardrop tattoo to drive the bus?
那個"神經病"是我丈夫
That "Psycho" is my husband.
那淚痕紋身是為祭奠蘇丹那些慘死的孩子
And the teardrop is a tribute to the lost children of Sudan.
所以  我希望能正式領養喜旺
So, I would like to officially adopt Hope.
我明白了
I see.
盡管我很想接這個案子
Well, as much as I would like to handle that...
但這可是很貴的
it's expensive.
這兩個人還欠我
And these two still owe me
上次狀告藍色牛仔公司
from when they sued the blue jean company
用紐扣代替拉鏈一案的律師費
over the "Button-fly."
不是吧  爹媽
Seriously, guys?
我很忙的
I'm a busy man
用紐扣太浪費我寶貴的時間
and those people have stolen minutes from my life.
我敢肯定他們打算付你錢的  對吧
I-I'm sure that they intend to pay you back... right?
你聽說過"伯特幣"嗎
Have you heard of something called "Burt Bucks"?
當然
Yes.
我就是那個讓你擺脫偽造罪名的律師
I'm the one that got you off the counterfeiting charge.
那個案子你也沒付我錢
You didn't pay me for that either.
我很遺憾  塞布麗娜
Well, sorry, Sabrina.
我看你永遠做不了喜旺的合法母親了
I guess you'll never be Hope's real mom.
我們盡力了
We tried.
等等  我剛剛突然想到
Wait, I'm starting to think
一個年輕性感的種馬或許不足以
that one hot, young stud might not be enough
贏下此案
to win this case.
我可以接領養案
So, I'll do the adoption,
除非你們愿意坐在我旁邊  扮演美麗的花瓶
if you two sit at my table as extra eye candy.
假扮律師肯定會超有趣的
It would be so fun to pretend to be lawyers.
或許我可以像艾麗·麥克比爾
I could be just like the one
在《甜心俏佳人》中的角色一樣
Ally McBeal played on that show.
我可以像《執法悍將》中的那個軍人一樣
I could be like that cool army guy on JAG.
我一直想找個借口穿白褲子
I've always wanted an excuse to wear white pants.
我們愿意
We'll do it.
有了你們這綠葉的陪襯
With you two lookers,
我就不需要打扮了
I won't need this anymore.
現在
Now...
你們誰能不能幫我
if one of you wouldn't mind helping me...
把這塊膠帶扯掉
pull off this tape.
有沃利在  我們終于可以
With Wally on board, we could finally
把領養手續辦下來了
make the adoption official.
多露出一點牙齒
How about a little more teeth?
完美
Perfect.
太棒了  我們可以拍一張正式照片呢
Cool, we get an official picture.
下一位
Next.
到我們了
That's us.
請收好
Here you go.
好了  再見
Okay, bye.
我  我以為你會
I... I thought you were gonna
讓我們宣誓
swear us in.
這不是個就職儀式
This isn't an inauguration.
那我們就拍照片好了
We'll just get to the picture then.
這個相機只用作公事用
This camera's only for official business.
不  我剛剛正式領養了這個小女孩  所以
No, I just officially adopted this little girl, so...
這個相機只是給官方打獵許可證使用的
For official hunting licenses.
明天開始就是乳鴿的季節了
Squab season starts tomorrow.
很好  那我們就申請一個全家的打獵許可證
Great, then we'll take one family hunting license, please.
你要去打乳鴿嗎
Are you going to go squab hunting?
是  你沒聽錯
Yes, you know what? Yes.
來這
Here, come on.
我們全家想要
My family and I would like
申請一個打乳鴿許可證  老娘才不管乳鴿是啥
one license to kill whatever a squab is.
我不給不打獵的人簽發許可證的
I don't issue licenses to non-hunters.
這樣搞會讓打獵證跌價的
It cheapens it.
別這樣嘛  說真的
Come on, honestly.
這對你來說能有多難啊
How hard is it really to just, like,
不就按下按鈕給我們
click your little button and take a picture
拍張照片嘛
of me and my family?
對了  我手機可以拍照啊
You know, I-I got a camera on my phone.
我們可以就在外面拍張照片
We could just take a picture outside.
他們有個漂亮的薔薇叢  還有那個
They got a-a nice rosebush, and that-that statue
一個瞎女人托著重物的雕像
of that blind woman holding weights.
只是
It just...
噢  你領養了一只小狗
Oh, someone's adopting a puppy.
我一定要拍張照片才行
I've got to get a picture of this.
哇靠
Oh, come on!
搞毛啊
Really?
那個波蘭紳士說道
This Polish gentlemen said,
我不知道那是個小丁丁
"I didn't know it was a penis."
不要笑
Hold for laughter.
先向陪審團行禮
Salute jury.
我在佛羅里達碰到這個律師
I saw this lawyer at a trial in Florida
在法庭上以一個敲門笑話開頭
open with a knock-knock joke.
相信我
Trust me.
效果贊爆了
It killed.
這樣如何  當你說"他無罪"時
How about when you say, "He's not guilty,"
我試著讓法庭上所有人說
I'll try to get the whole courtroom to say,
"他哪里無罪啊"
"How not guilty is he?"
不  不  不  不  你什么也別說
No, no, no, no. You-you say nothing.
但我們昨天一整晚都在看《大律師邁拉克》
But we stayed up all night watching Matlock.
律政美劇
伯特學南部律師很像的
Burt does a great Southern lawyer.
我叫布朗
My name is Brown.
我反對這個學校董事會
And I am against this board of education.
我佩服你所做的努力
I admire your commitment.
但我也知道對你來說
But I also know how difficult it is
穿帶紐扣門襟的褲子有多難
for you to button your fly.
所以
Therefore,
你閉嘴就好
you-you stay quiet.
我的天
My God.
她有兩個漂亮的手下
She's got one good-looking posse.
好了  就跟我們排練的一樣
All right, just like we practiced.
-法律顧問你好  -法律顧問你好
- Counselor.  - Counselor.
行了
Okay.
游戲開始了
Game on.
天  剛剛那下累死我了
Wow, that took a lot out of me.
當律師比我想得難多了
Being a lawyer's a lot harder than I thought.
現在我明白為什么他們按小時計費了
Now I know why they charge by the hour.
剛剛那下才  30秒左右吧
That was only, like, 30 seconds.
我就累壞了
I'm exhausted.
我分娩了四個小時
So, I'd been in labor for four hours
外面還下著大雨
and it's pouring rain outside.
但就在我的斯凱拉出生的那個瞬間
But right then when my Skylar was born,
一道閃電劃過窗戶
a ray of light came through the window.
我完全可以理解你所說的
I know exactly what you're talking about.
當你第一次看到喜旺時  你什么感覺
What was it like when you first saw Hope?
那真的很
It was really...
神奇
magical.
生喜旺可能是
Giving birth to Hope was
我這輩子做過最棒的事情了
probably the best thing I ever did with my life.
真的  我只是非常幸運
Really I was just lucky
能有吉米在旁幫我把喜旺拖出來
that Jimmy was there to help me push it out of my body.
你們倆上過育嬰課嗎
You guys took baby classes?
當然  我們上了  兩年課
Yeah, we took, uh, two years.
我跟吉米
Jimmy and I were very,
都把生孩子看得很重要
very serious about baby birth.
首先 當發現領養小孩不過是蓋幾個章時
First, she seemed upset that the adoption
她應該覺得很不爽
was just a rubber stamp.
接著  我知道的第二件事是
Then, next thing I know,
她說自己用母乳喂養喜旺
she's saying she breast-fed Hope
一天兩加侖[相當于7.5升]
two gallons of milk a day.
我不是專家
Now, I am no expert.
但這個量對一個95磅重的女人太多了吧
But this seems like a lot for a 95-pound woman.
塞布麗娜可能覺得自己錯過了
Maybe Sabrina feels like she missed out
母性中整個生孩子的部分吧
on the whole "Having a baby" Part of motherhood.
對
Yeah.
對于我們來說  生小孩不過是
To us, giving birth just seems like
一個痛苦的  惡心的
a painful, disgusting,
殘忍的生物學玩笑
cruel joke of biology.
但對于女人來說  那就是他們的"超級碗"啊
But to women, it's their Super Bowl.
超級碗  美國橄欖球聯盟決賽
當我的繼母跟塞布麗娜有同樣的想法時
When my non-birth mother was feeling the way Sabrina is,
我另一個媽會把她橄欖球隊的女孩叫到一起
my other mother got the ladies from her rugby team together
她們會給我繼母舉辦一個再生儀式的
and they threw her a rebirthing ceremony.
你到底想表達什么
Where do you go for that?
我的媽媽們去佛蒙特州
Well, my moms went to a bar
一個叫"安東尼沙龍"的酒吧
in Vermont called Saloon B. Anthony.
但你可以自己來嘛
But you could do it yourself.
我自己怎么做一個再生儀式啊
How am I supposed to do a rebirthing?
我還從來沒有看過真正的生產呢
I've never even seen an actual birth.
喜旺是在監獄里出生的
Hope was born in a jail.
我跟弗蘭克可以幫你
Frank and I could help you.
哦  當然
Oh, yeah, totally.
再生儀式很簡單
Rebirthing ceremonies are simple.
你懂的  有時失眠癥會驅使
Sometimes insomnia can drive a man
一個人進入網絡深處陰暗的角落的
to the deep dark corners of the Internet.
那個波蘭人說
That is when the Polish man said,
"我不知道那是個小丁丁"
"I didn't know it was a penis."
她偷了我的笑話
She stole my joke!
我整個開場白都是
My entire opening argument
基于這個笑話的
was built on that joke!
你們將要發現的唯一一件事情
...the only thing that you'll come to realize...
就是
is...
那個男人
that man,
鮑比·保曼
Bobby Bowman,
是個偷電動車的賊
is a moped thief.
我會跟你們證明
And I will prove that to you
這事兒簡直就是不言自明
beyond a shadow of a doubt.
菲普斯先生  你可以開始了
Mr. Phipps, your opening statement?
我有個更好的開場笑話
I have an even better opening joke.
但在我說之前
But before I tell it,
問下你們之間有誰被小丑調戲過嗎
have any of you ever been molested by a clown?
我沒什么好說的了
I've got nothing.
你辦得到的
You can do this.
記住  你沒必要說得那么好
Remember, you don't have to be that good
因為我們是如此漂亮
because we're that beautiful.
尊敬的陪審團
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
我跟我的
me and my...
引人注目  帥氣逼人的同事
noticeably handsome colleagues
有超過1000年的法學院學習經驗
have over 1,000 years of law school between the three of us.
我敢打賭你們肯定不會
I dare you to not be
在智力上
both intellectually
和身體上被同時喚醒
and physically aroused.
我說完了  法官大人
Nothing more, Your Honor...
因為我眼前全是星星
...because all I see are stars.
他怎么可能是無罪的
How not guilty is he?
別擔心  我死不了
Don't worry, I'm not gonna die.
有個神準的預言家告訴我
I have it on the authority of a very reputable fortune teller
我能活到...
that I would live to be...
等等  我多大了
Wait, how old am I?
至少在我們偽裝律師的職業生涯中
Well, at least our careers as pretend lawyers
還沒輸過一場官司
are ending without us ever losing a case.
我會想念這副眼鏡的
I'm really gonna miss these glasses.
它讓我覺得我是文化人
They make me feel so smart.
你們不能走啊
Wait, you guys cannot go.
我可沒錢再請其他律師了
I can't afford another lawyer.
我們真的很想幫你  但是
We really want to help, but...
我們不是你以為的那種律師
we're not the kind of lawyers you think we are.
那你們擅長打什么官司
Okay, so what's your specialty?
受害人很特殊的
Cases with special victims,
蓄意傷害之類的
criminals with intent.
你知道  上頭條的那種
You know, ripped from the headlines kind of stuff.
我是無辜的
Okay, look, I'm innocent.
只有你們能救我了
All right, you guys are my only hope.
這是玩真的
This is serious.
他需要我們
He needs us.
我知道  但我們幫不了
I know, but we can't do this.
超出我們的腦力了
We're in way over our heads.
知道她腦子里還有什么嗎
You know who else was in over her head?
《律政俏佳人》里的瑞茜·威瑟斯彭
Reese Witherspoon in Legally Blonde,
她從不放棄
and she never gave up.
還有《吉娃娃律師所》里的狗律師
Neither did the dog lawyer in Chihuahua Attorney:
正義之咬
Justice Bites.
如果那狗能打贏最高法院
And if that dog can win a case against the Supreme Court,
我們也能做到
we can do this.
法官大人
Your Highness,
即使菲普斯先生不在  我們也想繼續下
we'd like to continue on without Mr. Phipps.
請對我們要求松一點
Just be prepared to keep us on a short leash,
但您最后一定會明白我們的意思
but ultimately, you'll see where we're going
并且同意我們的觀點
with this and allow it.
還有幾步
Just a few more steps.
拜托是繩球  拜托是繩球
Ooh, please be a tetherball, please be a tetherball.
嚇死我了
Everything about this scares me.
吉米  這是搞什么
Jimmy, what the hell is going on?
是新生儀式
It's a rebirthing ceremony.
驚喜吧
Surprise!
我們要模仿分娩
We're going to simulate childbirth
讓你體驗一把做媽媽的感覺
so you can feel like a real mom.
歡迎來到你的超級碗
Welcome to your Super Bowl.
吉米  你為什么要這么做
Jimmy, why would you do this?
在市政廳的時候他們沒把我們的領養當回事
Because you seemed so upset at City Hall
我看你有點生氣
when they didn't make a big deal out of the adoption.
就覺得你需要更多
I thought that, you know, you wanted more
做母親的感覺
of a motherhood moment.
我只是氣他們的官僚作風
No, I-I just was upset about the bureaucracy of it.
憑什么又矮又胖的獵鴿犯能拍照  我們卻不能
Like, why should a squab killer get a photo and we don't?
那你為什么要騙斯凱拉和他的媽媽們
Why did you lie to the mothers of Skylar and Skylar?
我是說  我聽到你跟他們說
I mean, I heard you telling them
你是喜旺的親生媽媽
that you gave birth to Hope.
-你聽到了  -對
- Oh, you heard that? - Yeah.
其他媽媽都在說自己寶寶的故事
The other moms were talking about their baby stories,
我感覺自己都沒怎么參與過
and I just didn't feel like getting
喜旺的出生和成長
into the whole thing about Hope.
沒什么大不了的  只是
It's not a big deal, it's just...
我說謊是因為有時候說謊比坦白容易
Sometimes I lie when it's easier than telling the truth.
不做這個儀式我無所謂
Look, I'm all right if we don't do this,
但還有一個幫忙的人
but there was another person helping.
她都排練了一天了
She's been practicing all day.
搞毛啊
What the heck?
好吧
All right, fine.
那咱開始吧  因為
Then let's get to it because...
你的羊水破了
...your water just broke.
倫諾克斯先生  你能指出
Mr. Lennox, would you point to the man
偷你電動車的那個人嗎
you saw steal your moped?
彎腰系鞋帶
Bend down and tie your shoe.
我確定他也會把手放低的
I'm pretty sure he'd just point lower.
請記錄  倫諾克斯先生
Let the record show that Mr. Lennox
指向了被告
pointed to the defendant.
沒用
That didn't work.
玩《法律與秩序》里的"我收回"那招
Do that "Withdrawn" trick they do on Law and Order.
對對
Yeah, yeah.
倫諾克斯先生
Mr. Lennox,
你的愛好是斬掉狗狗的頭  這是真的嗎
is it true that you decapitate puppies as a hobby?
我收回
Withdrawn.
你是塔利班的成員吧
Weren't you a member of the Taliban?
我收回
Withdrawn.
你有戀童癖  我收回
A pedophile? Withdrawn.
是個賊  我收回
A thief? Withdrawn.
曾在鱷梨園里大便
Defecated in an avocado field?
我收回
Withdrawn.
吉斯先生  你夠了啊
Mr. Chance, enough of this.
尼瑪《法律與秩序》
Damn Law and Order
把整代律師全給毀了
ruined an entire generation of lawyers.
休庭
I'm calling a recess.
休庭耶
Ooh, recess.
出去溜達十分鐘
Maybe it would be good for us to go outside
應該不錯
and run around for about ten minutes.
好了  開始宮縮
Okay, contractions are starting.
你想自然分娩還是打麻藥
You gonna go natural or you want some drugs?
等等  你們真有麻藥嗎
Wait, do you actually have drugs?
沒時間打麻藥了
There's no time for drugs!
寶寶要出來了
This baby's coming!
勇敢一點
Brace yourselves.
呼吸  塞布麗娜
Breathe, Sabrina.
親愛的加油  你可以的
Come on, baby, you can do it.
還真有點激動  吉米
This is actually kind of exciting, Jimmy.
呼吸得很好
Yeah, your breathing is great.
找準一個點  然后盯著它
Now, pick a focal point and stare at it.
厲害吧  我看過專業書
Yeah, I read a book.
我很慶幸沒打麻藥
I'm really glad we didn't take those drugs.
因為親身感受這個過程
I feel like it's really important
對我來說真的很重要
for me to be present through this.
做完這個  我就成人造陰道領域的權威了
When this is over, I call dibs on the faux-gina.
我要多幫助那些不孕不育的夫妻
I want to do more of these for deserving barren couples.
好了  來吧
Okay, here we go.
-我們要有寶寶了  -我知道
- We are having a baby! - I know!
快點好嗎
But soon, right?
她在管子里待了有一會兒了吧
'Cause I feel like she's been in that tube for a while.
媽咪  我卡住了
Mommy, I'm stuck!
什么
What?
她怎么會被卡住
Wait, how can she be stuck?
實事求是地說
In the spirit of realism,
管子可能被人用意面塞滿了
someone may have stuffed the tube with spaghetti.
什么  為什么要這么做
What? Why would you do something like that?
在馬后炮之前  我提醒一下
Before we start Monday morning quarterbacking,
這主意是我們一起在一個下午里想出來的
just remember we threw this together in an afternoon.
喜旺  撐住
Hope, hang on.
爸比來了
Daddy's coming.
于是我從窗戶望出去
And so I looked out the window,
就看到他在偷我的電動車
and that's when I saw him steal my moped.
你最后一次擦窗戶是什么時候
And when was the last time that window was cleaned?
窗戶是開著的
The window was open.
那倒是非常方便
That's very convenient.
請記錄
Let the record show
那真是非常方便
that that was very convenient.
完了  電視里演過的各種法律手段我們都用盡了
We're screwed. We've tried every legal maneuver
包括《法律與秩序》《波士頓法律》
we've ever seen on Law and Order, Boston Legal,
還有《生活的真相》
even that episode of Facts of Life
托蒂被種族歸納的那集
where Tootie got racially profiled.
那家伙根本就是在撒謊
That guy is totally lying.
我都不知道該叫還是哭了
I don't know whether to scream or cry.
有了
That's it.
你個騙子  倫諾克斯
You're a liar, Lennox,
我要讓你
and I am gonna
從主要證人淪落為
bust you down from star witness to loser
只能租《證人》看的慫貨
who rents the movie Witness.
你怎么能把一個無辜的人送入監獄
How can you send an innocent man to jail?
他身材瘦弱
He has a slight frame
相貌清秀
and delicate features,
當個內衣模特倒是非常合適
and that's great for an underwear model,
但當囚犯就太糟糕了
but it is horrible for a prisoner.
等等
Wait a minute.
我快瘋了
It's been driving me crazy.
我就覺得這場面有點熟悉
I knew I recognized you guys from somewhere.
我見過你們對一個交通女警耍這伎倆
I saw you work this routine on a meter maid.
老娘就讓你從一個
I will have you busted down from meter maid
交通女警變成一個家庭女傭
to regular maid, and trust me,
我可告訴你  野餐都用不起桌布
that is a picnic without a blanket.
糟了  這招不管用
Oh, crap, this isn't gonna work.
他知道"紅臉警 白臉警"這招了
He knows about "Bad cop, sad cop."
怎么這么長時間
What's taking so long?
很滑啊
Oh, it's really slippery.
我試試...
Oh, here, maybe if I try to...
我無法呼吸了
Ah, I can't breathe!
我不能呼吸了
I can't breathe!
線纜把他的脖子纏住了
The cord is wrapped around his neck!
我們得立馬把他拉出來
We got to get him out of there right away!
塞布麗娜  用力推  用盡全力去推
Sabrina, push, push with all your might!
你可以的  用力點
You can do it! Harder!
天哪  不敢相信你們這群白癡會認為這樣管用
God, I can't believe you idiots thought this would work!
塞布麗娜  有時候我覺得你忘了我是你老板
Sabrina, sometimes I think you forget I'm your boss.
媽咪  救命
Mama, help us.
我得采取點措施
I have to do something.
沒事了  沒事了
It's okay, it's okay.
你沒事了  媽咪在呢
You're okay; Mommy's got you.
是個男孩
It's a boy!
如果你同意
So, if you'll agree
免除這些罰單
to dismiss all these tickets,
我們一定可以讓我們的當事人認罪
we can definitely get our client to plead guilty.
一般來說  認罪協議不能幫被告律師
Traditionally, plea deals do not help the defendant's lawyers
免于支付停車罰款
avoid paying parking fines.
我知道了
I got it!
我們拒絕協議
We reject the deal.
我并沒有提出協議
I offered no deal.
賈妮斯  記錄下來
Janice, get it on the record
我并沒有向任何人提出協議
that I did not offer anyone a deal.
根據你之前的證詞
According to your previous testimony,
你看到我的當事人
when exactly did you see my client
在松樹街偷你電動車的具體時間是什么
stealing your moped on Pine Street?
5月19日下午五點
May 19th, 5:00 p.m.
那你的證詞里是否也曾說過
And is it also your testimony
你看到我德高望重的律師丈夫和我本人
that you saw my esteemed lawyer husband and myself,
在法律界也是受人敬重的律師
also an esteemed attorney at law,
在榆木大道收到罰單
getting a ticket on Elmwood Avenue?
-是的  -那能請你為我讀一讀
- Yes. - Would you mind reading
這張罰單上印著什么嗎
what's printed on this ticket for me?
5月19日下午五點
"May 19, 5:00 p.M."
女士們先生們
Ladies and gentlemen...
一個人怎么可能
...how could one man
在同一時間身處于相隔十英里的
be in two different places, ten miles apart from each other,
兩個地方呢
at the exact same time?
是因為
Is it because,
我猜一下  他有月光寶盒嗎
I don't know, he has a time machine?
又或者他在撒謊
Or is it because he is a liar?
好了
Fine!
我承認
I admit it.
我撒謊了
I lied.
我沒看到他偷我的電動車
I didn't see him steal my moped.
我那么說是因為
I just said it because
那個狗娘養的睡了我的女朋友
that son of a bitch slept with my girlfriend.
案件駁回
Case dismissed.
這是我的臺詞
I'm supposed to say that.
你在哭呢
Oh, you're crying.
我沒想到這對你有這么重大的意義
I thought this wasn't that big of a deal for you.
我撒謊了
I lied.
我說謊是因為有時候說謊比坦白容易
Sometimes I lie when it's easier than telling the truth.
我  我很抱歉  如果我太過分了的話
I'm-I'm sorry if-if I went a little overboard.
沒有
I'm not.
喜旺出生的時候
Neither of us was there
我們都不在身邊  但是
the first time Hope was born, and...
很奇怪的是
in a really weird way,
我覺得這對我們都是好事
I feel like it was good for all of us.
因為這次我們一起完成了
'Cause we did it together.
像一個真正的家庭
Like a real family.
所以這算是個好主意嗎
So this was good idea?
不  這主意糟透了
No, it was a horrible idea.
但是很管用
But it worked.
你這樣做  真是世界上最貼心的男人呢
And you are the sweetest man in the world for doing it.
喜旺的再出生給了我們
Hope's rebirth gave us something
都需要的東西
that we both needed.
我們一起做一些
The experience of doing something together
以前誰都沒做過的事
that neither of us had done before.
不止我們這樣
And we weren't the only ones.
你覺得我們現在該怎么處理這眼鏡
What do you think we should do with these now?
我想我們該扔了
I guess we get rid of them.
我們應該不會再假裝律師了
We're probably not gonna pretend to be lawyers again.
但戴眼鏡讓我覺得我是文化人
They just made me feel so smart.
不止是眼鏡的問題
Hey, it wasn't just the glasses.
你太棒了
You were amazing.
你比職業律師還聰明
You outsmarted professional lawyers.
你拯救了一個無辜的人  讓他免入冤獄
You kept an innocent man from going to jail.
不是我一個人的功勞
It wasn't just me.
如果不是你想到"壞警察  可憐蛋"那招
If you hadn't thought of doing "Bad cop, sad cop,"
亞倫根本不在場的事情就不會自己暴露了
then Aaron would've never blown his alibi.
我相信我們本來是可以當律師的
You know, I bet we could've been lawyers,
如果我們以前選擇不同的道路
if we'd done things differently.
比如去上法學院啊
Like go to law school and college
讀完高中什么的
and finished high school.
聽起來得花大力氣呢
That sounds like a lot of effort.
那吊帶褲磨得我好疼啊
And those suspenders chafed.
是啊  還有那些姿勢
Yeah, and all that posing...
我的嘴唇好疼
My lips hurt.
我覺得我嘴撇得過頭了
I think I over-pouted.
是啊  很高興我退休前沒輸過一場官司
Yeah, I'm happy to retire having never lost a case.
是啊  我也是
Yeah, me, too.
但我覺得我要等到明早再扔掉眼鏡
But I think I'll wait till morning to throw these out.
好主意
Good idea.
也許我們可以戴著眼鏡睡覺
Maybe if we sleep in 'em,
這樣會做聰明的夢
we'll have smart dreams.